<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<pack:associatedspecifications xmlns:pack="urn:pack">
	<pack:associatedspecification name="Generic CDA" ref="GenericCDA/index.html">
		<pack:description>The Generic CDA Domain Message Specification contains details on the "on-the-wire" format for CDA payloads. The "on-the-wire" format is the actual payload structure that is sent to a recipient. The Generic CDA Domain Message Specification documents two "on-the-wire" CDA formats. The first is for use over the Transaction Messaging System (TMS) when using TMS wrappers, this is documented in the Generic CDA Domain Message Specification as "NPfIT CDA RMIM - POCD_MT000001UK04". The second is used for non-TMS usage and is documented in the Generic CDA Domain Message Specification as "NHS CDA RMIM - POCD_MT000002UK01".</pack:description>
	</pack:associatedspecification>
	<pack:associatedspecification name="Nullification" ref="Nullification/index.html">
		<pack:description>
			The Nullification Domain Message Specification contains details on how to nullify a CDA document that was, for example, sent in error or a document that is not accepted by a recipient. The domain specifies the message definition of the nullification document ("Nullification Document - POCD_MT130001UK05"), which is generically used to nullify any CDA document.
		</pack:description>
	</pack:associatedspecification>
	<pack:associatedspecification name="Distribution Envelope" ref="DistributionEnvelope/index.html">
		<pack:description>
			The Distribution Envelope Specification defines the constraints to be applied to the distribution envelope when used with ITK Correspondence content.
		</pack:description>
	</pack:associatedspecification>
	<pack:associatedspecification name="ITK Business Acknowledgement" ref="ITKBusinessAcknowledgement/index.html">
		<pack:description>
This Domain Message Specification documents the business acknowledgement for use within ITK messaging.
The business acknowledgement is triggered by the presence of a handling specification with a key "urn:nhs-itk:ns:201005:ackrequested" and value set to "true" in the distribution envelope of a received transmission. The business acknowledgement is sent using the service "SendBusinessAck-v1-0". A key feature of the ITK Business Acknowledgement is that it is capable of acknowledging individual payloads within a received message.
		</pack:description>
	</pack:associatedspecification>
	<pack:associatedspecification name="CDA Implementation Guidance Narrative Block Tags
" ref="NarrativeBlockTagsGuidance/index.html">
		<pack:description>This pack gives guidance on the use of tags and attributes used in a CDA text section (also called CDA markup).The content of this pack is based on the schema "NarrativeBlock.xsd", which is included in Domain Message Specifications in the "dt" folder. This schema is included in the Generic CDA and Profile schemas to ensure the correct CDA mark-up has been applied to the text element within the section class.</pack:description>
	</pack:associatedspecification>
	<pack:associatedspecification name="Technical Guidance for Templated CDA Domains" ref="TechnicalGuidance.pdf">
		<pack:description>
			Technical Guidance for Templated CDA Domains gives detailed technical information required to implement a HSCIC CDA templated domain. This document only forms part of the documentation required to implement a HSCIC CDA domain and should be used in conjunction with the message specification and the domain baseline document set.
		</pack:description>
	</pack:associatedspecification>
	<pack:associatedspecification name="Multi Payload Message Specification" ref="MultiPayloadMessageSpecification.pdf">
		<pack:description>
			Multi Payload Message Specification gives detailed technical information about the use of mult payloads within HSCI messaging.This document only forms part of the documentation required to implement a HSCIC CDA domain and should be used in conjunction with the message specification and the domain baseline document set.
		</pack:description>
	</pack:associatedspecification>
	<pack:associatedspecification name="Additional Guidance for HSCI messaging" ref="AdditionalGuidanceForHSCIMessaging.pdf">
		<pack:description>
This document gives additional guidance relevant to HSCI messaging. This is information such as additional message receiver responsilbilies or business rules.
		</pack:description>
	</pack:associatedspecification>
	<pack:associatedspecification name="Distribution Envelope with Payloads Requiring a Business Acknowledgment" ref="Distribution Envelope with Payloads Requiring a Business Acknowledgment.pdf">
		<pack:description>
This document contains example guidance on how to populate the Distribution Envelope when a Business Acknowledgment is required.
		</pack:description>
	</pack:associatedspecification>
		<pack:associatedspecification name="SCCI2075 ADW Dataset Definition to Message Attribute Mapping" ref="Data to message attribute mapping.pdf">
		<pack:description>
This document contains guidance on how to map the SCCI2075 ADW Dataset to the HL7 V3 message attributes.
		</pack:description>
	</pack:associatedspecification>
</pack:associatedspecifications>
