<pack:associatedspecifications xmlns:pack="urn:pack">
	<pack:associatedspecification name="Generic CDA" ref="GenericCDA/index.html">
		<pack:description>
			The Generic CDA Domain Message Specification contains details on the "on-the-wire" format for CDA payloads. The "on-the-wire" format is the actual payload structure that is sent to a recipient. The Generic CDA Domain Message Specification documents two "on-the-wire" CDA formats. The first is for use over the Transaction Messaging System (TMS) when using TMS wrappers, this is documented in the Generic CDA Domain Message Specification as "NPfIT CDA RMIM - POCD_MT000001UK04". The second is used for non-TMS usage and is documented in the Generic CDA Domain Message Specification as "NHS CDA RMIM - POCD_MT000002UK01".
		</pack:description>
	</pack:associatedspecification>
	<pack:associatedspecification name="Standards for the clinical structure and content of patient records" ref="Standards-for-the-clinical-structure-and-content-of-patient-records.pdf">
		<pack:description>
This document describes standards for the structure and content of patient records, covering hospital referral letters, inpatient clerking, handover communications, discharge summaries and outpatient letters. They have been developed using published evidence and consultation with doctors, patients, nurses and allied healthcare professionals. The standards were signed off as fit for purpose for the whole medical profession by the Academy of Medical Royal Colleges (www.aomrc.org.uk) in April 2013.
		</pack:description>
	</pack:associatedspecification>
	<pack:associatedspecification name="Technical Guidance for Templated CDA Domains" ref="TechnicalGuidance.pdf">
		<pack:description>
			Technical Guidance for Templated CDA Domains gives detailed technical information required to implement a HSCIC CDA templated domain. This document only forms part of the documentation required to implement a HSCIC CDA domain and should be used in conjunction with the message specification and the domain baseline document set.
		</pack:description>
	</pack:associatedspecification>
	<pack:associatedspecification name="CDA Implementation Guidance Narrative Block Tags
" ref="NarrativeBlockTagsGuidance/index.html">
		<pack:description>This pack gives guidance on the use of tags and attributes used in a CDA text section (also called CDA markup).The content of this pack is based on the schema "NarrativeBlock.xsd", which is included in Domain Message Specifications in the "dt" folder. This schema is included in the Generic CDA and Profile schemas to ensure the correct CDA mark-up has been applied to the text element within the section class.</pack:description>
	</pack:associatedspecification>
	<pack:associatedspecification name="Populating HSCIC CDA Document Participant Templates" ref="DDM-G-044 PopulatingDocumentParticipantTemplates.pdf">
		<pack:description>
		This provides guidance on how to populate the generic participant class to assist implementers of HSCIC CDA based domain message specifications.
		</pack:description>
	</pack:associatedspecification>
</pack:associatedspecifications>
